Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 13.11.23 13:03:41
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：非燕   苏小黛   川川   zhanginfo   肉松
■
校对：苏小黛   时间轴：紫熏   新月
后期：冰河     监制：wdjmhs
■
国土安全
第三季 第二集
美国空军及海军
Air and naval forces of the United States
对恐怖组织发起了一系列攻击
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
泛美航空103号班机于洛克比失事
Pan Am Flight 103 crashed into the the town of Lockerbie.
他已批准在非洲  欧洲和中东的恐怖行动
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe, the Middle East.
我们不容科威特遭受侵略
This will not stand, this aggression against Kuwait.
我们将一视同仁
We will make no distinction.
美国军舰科尔号
The USS Cole was attacked
在亚丁湾港口加油时遭到袭击
while refueling in the port of Aden.
这是恐怖主义行动
This was an act of terrorism.
这是可鄙懦弱的行动
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
下面为您演奏的
The next song we're going to play for you
是一首经典曲目
is one of the good old favorites.
直到他受到了阻击
Until something stops him.
就在我眼前
It was right in front of my eyes,
我万万没想到
and I never saw it coming.
该飞机撞向了世贸中心
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
成千上万的民众东奔西逃
Thousands of people running.
我们必须  也将在国内外保持警惕
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
你是我见过最聪明
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person
又最愚蠢的人
I've ever known.
我不是不明真相的那个人
I'm not the one who got it wrong.
我是唯一的明白人
I'm the only one who got it right.
拿下
Take 'em.
统统拿下
Take 'em all.
《国土安全》前情提要
Previously on Homeland...
中情局总部遭袭至今已有58天
It's been 58 days since the attack on Langley
219名美国人在此次袭击中丧生
in which 219 americans lost their lives.
中情局连自己都保护不了
How can the CIA be expected to protect this country,
又怎么能保护这个国家呢
if it can't even protect itself?
对于我们来说  她之前不听指挥
Her history of insubordination and mental illness
又有精神病史  这可能比在特别委员会面前
might be more useful to us than a good performance
有良好表现更为有用
in front of the select committee.
我做不到
I won't do that.
我不能把卡莉扔出去当挡箭牌
I won't throw Carrie under the bus.
丹娜上个月进展明显
Dana has made great progress over the last month.
非常棒
She's doing well.
你是说对于那种在浴缸割腕的人而言吧
You mean for someone who got in a bathtub and tried to slit her wrists?
什么时候才能再见到你
When can I see you again?
他叫马吉德・贾瓦迪
Yeah, his name is Majid Javadi.
另外这六人经他纠集织建网络
The other six make up the network he put together
策划并实施了对当局总部的袭击
to plan and carry out the attacks on Langley.
拿下他们
Take 'em.
你有没有看今天的报纸
Have you seen the paper yet?
今天的头条是
Alright, now, the headline is:
"中情局本部引爆者与中情局人员有染"
"CIA officer linked to langley bomber."
我猜你已经看过这个了
I assume you've seen this.
谁不知道我们多讨厌有事情被捅到媒体上去
We all know how we hate things getting out into the press,
当然了  除非是我们自己把事情捅出去的
Unless of course we put them out there ourselves.
卡莉  你在犯一个很严重的错误
Carrie, you're making a bad mistake.
操你妈的  操你们全家
Fuck you! Fuck all of you!
或许你应该评论一下昨天报纸上的
Perhaps you'd care to comment on the article
一篇文章
in yesterday's paper.
受质疑的谍报人员
The case officer in question,
她被诊断为躁郁症
she's been diagnosed as bipolar.
这一情况  她对上级
A condition she concealed from her superiors
-一直隐瞒了十多年  -她是否向你隐瞒了
- for more than ten years. - Did she conceal from you
她和布洛迪议员发生性关系一事
the fact that she was sleeping with Congressman Brody?
我恐怕她确实隐瞒过  是的
I'm afraid she did, yes.
上帝
God...
-卡莉  -我得和索尔谈谈  索尔
- Carrie.  -I need to talk to Saul. Saul!
-他不在家  卡莉  -索尔
- He's not here, Carrie. - Saul!
他不在家
He's not here.
他已经走了  清早有个会
He left already. He had some early morning meeting.
-和谁  -不知道
- With whom? - I don't know.
-可以给他打电话  -如果我能联系到他
- We could call him. - Well, if I could call him,
还大老远跑来这里干什么
why would I come all the way here?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
告诉索尔我来过
Well, tell Saul I came by.
他肯定预料到了
I'm sure he knows.
你们俩这是怎么了
What is going on with you two?
索尔给我说了那件事
Saul told me about the incident.
-哪件事  -餐馆里的事
- What incident? - At the restaurant.
那件事啊
Oh, that.
-他说你很生气  -是啊
- He said you were very upset. - Well, yeah.
我想是的
I-I guess I was.
但是如果要我说一件
But, you know, if-if I think about an incident
让我生气的事
that's upsetting to me,
不是这件  而是他在参议院特别委员会前
no, I think it would have to be when he sold me down the river
把我给彻底出卖了
in front of the fucking senate select committee.
这才
Now, that...
这才叫我生气
that was upsetting.
一定要告诉他我来过
Be sure to tell him I came by.
卡莉
Carrie...
我给过他机会了
Uh, he had his chance.
他们一无所获
So they found nothing.
别心急
So far.
这么多资料都没用  包括这该死的笔记本
Out of all this, including a damn laptop.
我们找了位专家
We're bringing in a specialist.
她会有所发现的
She'll find something.
我杀了个九岁的孩子  她最好能有所发现
There's a nine-year-old dead. She better.
你们好
Hello?
-这是B会议室吗  -是的
- Is this conference B? - Yeah.
你是法拉
You're Fara?
是的
Yes.
我是索尔・贝伦森  这位是彼得・奎恩
I'm Saul Berenson. This is Peter Quinn.
有什么不对吗
Is something wrong?
没事
No.
我得去处理这个
I got to take care of this.
彼得  你给她介绍一下情况
Peter, you'll get her up to speed?
好
Sure.
你来这里工作多久了
So, how long have you worked here?
第一天起
Since the first.
今年吗
Of the year?
是这个月
Of the month.
才八天
Eight days.
我们的汇报专家到了
Our transactions expert arrived.
她怎么样
How is she?
一个带着头巾的孩子
A kid in a headscarf.
大多数的分局骨干都在爆炸中丧生了
And most of the banking division vanished in the explosion.
你要找一个有语言技能的专家
You asked for a specialist with language skills.
这个就是了
That's what you get.
你那边什么情况
So, what do you got?
卡莉
Carrie.
她联系了一个记者
She called a reporter.
显然  她认为有必要让他们
Apparently, she thinks it's important they,
用她的话说是  "听听她的说法"
quote, "Hear her side of the story."
她透露什么事了吗
She give any indication what that is?
还没  但你也知道她会说什么
Not yet, but you know what she's gonna say.
我们从头至尾都知道布洛迪是恐怖分子
We knew Brody was a terrorist all along.
他穿了一件自杀式背心
He wore a suicide vest into a bunker
和副总统走进地堡
with the vice president.
她试图警告我们  可没人听她的
She tried to warn us; nobody would listen.
那就打电话给编辑  让他把这事盖过去
So call the editor; get him to shut it down.
她不到黄河心不死  索尔
She's out for blood, Saul.
我们搞定了这些人
We keep her away from these guys,
她还会另求他路
she just goes somewhere else.
听着
Look,
我们料到会有这情况
we knew this might happen.
我们有应对措施
We planned for it.
我只想告诉你我会阻止她
I just wanted you to know I'm gonna stop her.
好了  你要知道
Okay, I'd like you to acknowledge
我在录音
that I am recording this
你说的一切都会记录在案
and that everything you say is on the record.
嗯  我正在被录音
Yeah, I'm being recorded.
我看到红灯亮了
I see the red light,
我想要全都录下来
and I want everything on the record.
我是妮可・黄  坐在我对面的是...
I'm Nicole Hung, here with...
卡莉・麦吉森
Carrie Mathison.
你在中情局工作了14年
You've been with the CIA 14 years.
是的
Yes.
你说你最近发生了意外
You told me you had a falling out recently.
不  我说的是
No, what I said was
我受到了攻击
I'm under attack.
一周前  你发表了一篇文章
A week ago, you published a story
说中情局本部引爆者
that an unnamed CIA officer was in a romantic relationship
与中情局人员有染
with the Langley bomber.
那人就是你吗
And is that officer you?
不  你没抓到重点
No, you're missing the point.
中情局没有人
No one at the CIA was
和中情局本部引爆者有染
in a relationship with the Langley bomber.
好吧  等等  根据我的消息来源
Okay, wait, according to my source...
就是中情局
The CIA.
我不能给你肯定的答案
I can't confirm that.
我不知道你打算
Well, I don't know what kind of conversation
怎么把谈话继续下去
you expect to have here
如果你都不肯承认再明显不过的事实
if you won't acknowledge the fucking obvious.
CIA是故意把报道透漏给你来陷害我的
The CIA gave you that story to set me up.
他们这么做有什么好处
For what?
弥天大谎
The big lie.
听着  不管他们说了什么
Now, despite what they said,
尼古拉斯・布洛迪
Nicholas brody is not responsible
与中情局的爆炸无关
For the explosion at langley.
你有证据
And you can prove this?
没错  我就是为这个来的
Yeah, that's why I'm here.
索尔・贝伦森在去委员会作证前
Did Saul Berenson know
知道这事吗
When he testified before the senate subcommittee?
他当然知道
Of course he did.
他说的一切都是谎话
Everything he said was bullshit.
我不是不明真相的那个人
Now, I'm not the one who got it wrong.
我才是唯一的明白人
I'm the only one who got it right,
而在此前非常长的时间内
And for the longest time,
CIA没有一个人肯信我
I couldn't get anyone at the CIA to believe me.
你告诉别人我要来了吗
Did you tell anyone that I was coming here?
只有我的编辑
Just my editor.
只有你的编辑
Just your editor?
操你妈的索尔
Fucking Saul.
卡莉・麦吉森
Carrie Mathison,
我们是警察
D.C. Metro.
你得跟我们走一趟
You need to come with us.
怎么  就来三个人
what, three of you?
你们觉得这点人就够了吗
You think that's enough?
只是例行公事  女士
Standard procedure, ma'am.
什么公事
Yeah, for-for what?
他们又给我编了个什么罪名
What sort of bullshit charges did they make up?
没有什么罪名  女士
There's no charges, ma'am.
我们有一份精神科拘留令
We've got a psychiatric detention order.
您明白是什么吗
You understand what that is?
明白  我明白
Yeah, I understand.
不用了
Hey, that's not necessary.
您会配合吧
Is it?
您有权在24小时内召开听证会
Now, you're entitled to a full commitment hearing within 24 hours.
这他妈就是个陷阱
This is complete bullshit!
你心知肚明  对吧
You know that, right?
女士  请
Ma'am, please.
你们回家有多久了  快一周了吧
So, you've been back home now, what, almost a week?
还好吗
How's that going?
会很困难吗
Is it a challenge?
为什么会困难
Why would it be a challenge?
我也不知道
I don't know.
再次回到现实世界中来
Reentry, being back out in the world?
我可不在现实世界中
I'm not back out in the world though.
我一直被困在家里
I'm stuck at home.
为什么会这样呢
And why is that?
丹娜觉得她是个...典型的反面
Dana thinks that she's... Famous in a bad way.
我说的是"反面教材"
The word is "Infamous."
是吗  你觉得自己是个反面教材吗
Is that what you think, that you're infamous?
好吧  不  我不觉得
Okay. No, I'm not.
那是什么
Well, which is it?
好吧  来回顾一下
Well, let's see.
我爸炸了CIA  杀了三百多人
My dad blew up the CIA, he killed 300 people,
人称第二次911
They call it the second 9/11, and it was
有很长一段时间  这是街头巷尾的唯一话题
All anybody talked about for a month and a half.
这是你爸做的事
What your dad did?
没错
Right.
那你自己做的事呢
What about what you did?
我  这个吗
What I did? This?
比较起来  这完全不值一提了吧
By comparison, it's, like, nothing.
我知道你的意思  但这并非不值一提
I know what you mean by that, but it's not nothing.
这也是我们三个今天共聚在此的原因
It's why we're here, the three of us.
那么你呢
So, what about you?
我
Me?
还是那个问题  你怎么样
Same question. How are you doing?
我很好
I'm fine.
好吧
Okay.
真的
Really.
我很高兴她回来了
I'm just glad that she's home.
很好
Good.
的确  事情有些变化
I mean, there have been some adjustments,
但我们知道这是在所难免的
But we knew there would be.
什么样的变化
What kind of adjustments?
她重装了浴室
She remodeled the bathroom...
就是我自杀的地方
Where I did it.
我没有
I didn't.
你明明就有  你把它整个重装了
Yeah, you did. You remodeled the whole thing.
我没有
I didn't.
我没有重装
I didn't remodel it.
渗入水泥的血迹擦不干净
The blood wouldn't come out of the grout,
我只能把它们都换了  是我自己看书学做的
So I had to replace everything, which I did myself with a book.
没必要再说这事了
We don't have to talk about that.
同意
With you there.
你好  我想预约
Hi. I need to make an appointment
理查森医生  周二
For, um, Thursday for Dr. Richardson.
我想你
I miss you.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
丹娜  走吧
Dana, come on.
卡莉・麦吉森  我是哈伦医生
Carrie Mathison, I'm Dr. Harlan.
哈伦  我识字
Harlan. I can read.
我会陪你出席明天的拘禁听证会
I'll be with you tomorrow at your commitment hearing.
我想向你解释一下
I'd like to explain to you what that is.
我知道什么是拘禁听证会
I know what a commitment hearing is.
我只是不敢相信他们真要这么干
I just can't believe they're actually going through with it.
我不太明白你的意思
I'm not sure what you mean.
我的意思是  我懂
Well, I mean, I get it.
有人想说出真相
Someone tries to tell the truth,
你们就说他们是疯子
You counter by calling them crazy.
我很欣赏这招  真体面
I admire the move; it's elegant, but it's...
不过真的没必要
It's unnecessary.
告诉他们吧
Tell them that.
我退出
I'm standing down.
你退出
You're standing down?
我受到教训了  能让我走了吗
I've learned my lesson, so can I get out of here, please?
这里说你停止服药了
Says here you stopped taking your meds.
哪里说  什么  那是什么
Says where? What? What? What is that?
你的病历
It's your medical history.
谁给的病历
According to whom?
你的医生们
Your doctors.
是吗  可是...
Really? 'cause...
我真正去看的医生
No doctor of mine, one that I am actually seeing,
没人会那样写的
Would write that.
你有停止用药吗
Did you stop taking your meds?
我没有  我不是单纯的停药
I didn't... I didn't just stop taking my meds.
我用了另一套方法来代替药物
I have a routine to compensate.
这方法是我的医生建议的
A routine that I have worked out
我真正的医生  不是什么CIA的骗子
With my actual doctor, not some CIA shill
他们就是想让我闭嘴
Who's trying to shut me up.
我每天都跑步  跑六英里
I, um... I run every day, six miles.
有时候还更多
Sometimes more.
我还唱歌  想不到吧
Singing helps. Go figure.
还有  我还冥想
And, um, and I meditate.
以此保持冷静
To stay calm.
是吗  你冷静吗
Are you... Calm?
考虑到
Well, considering
我正被铐在医院的轮床上
I'm chained to a gurney in a hospital gown,
我想说我能保持这样已经不只是冷静了
I'd say I'm beyond calm.
我他妈都快入定了
I'm fucking zen!
我只是...  我不...
I just... I can't...
我不能再用药了
I can't do the meds anymore.
为什么
Why not?
因为那会让我的脑子变得迟钝
Because they dull my head.
我做事的时候会忽视重点
I miss things when I'm on them.
不是忽视
Miss, not... As in "Yearn for,"
是"抓不住"
But miss as in "Fail to see."
-抓不住  比如什么  -比如
- Fail to see what, for example? - Well, for example,
中情局的爆炸导致了219人丧生
The explosion at langley that killed 219 people.
我看到了
And I see it already,
你脸上的怀疑  可我真是名CIA
The doubt on your face, but I-I am cia.
你可以去查证
You can verify it.
当然
Unless, of course,
除非他们抹去了我的档案
They expunged my records, which...
仔细想想  可能性非常大
...Come to think of it, is a real possibility.
听着  我妹妹是名医生
Look, my sister is a doctor.
你可以给她打电话
You can call her.
她会告诉你我说的一切都是真的
She'll tell you everything I've said is true.
他们说你在找我
They said you were looking for me?
希望没有打扰到您
I didn't want to bother you.
不会  发现什么了
No bother. What do you got?
我设法追踪了笔记本上的账户
I managed to source all the accounts on the laptop.
并没有很多
There weren't that many.
文件也都在公文包里
And the documents in the briefcase, too.
结论是
And?
没有与伊朗有关的东西
Nothing originates in iran.
等你发现了再告诉我
Let me know when you find something that does.
长官
Sir?
我不太明白您到底希望我找什么
I'm not sure what you expect me to do.
我已经照您的要求浏览了所有账户
I've looked at all the accounts like you asked.
没有任何异常
There's nothing there.
知道为什么找你来吗
You know what you're here for?
检查银行账目
To examine the bank records.
你要跟踪钱的流向
You're following the money.
从香港贷款银行到这个男人
From Hong Hong lending bank to this guy.
这儿
Here.
马吉德・贾瓦迪
Majid Javadi.
这个伊朗人资助了12月12号的那场
The Iranian who funded the attack on this agency
对中情局的袭击活动
That occurred on 12/12.
我知道
I know.
很好
Good.
那就好好干吧
So do that.
还有
And you know what else?
我们说的是
While we're talking about an event
一场造成两百名美国公民死亡的袭击事件
That left 200 americans dead on the ground,
而目前你所做的一切  似乎都是无用功
And what you're doing about it, which is apparently nothing...
请原谅我态度不好
forgive me.
你头上戴的那玩意儿
You wearing that thing on your head
对于那些本该成为你的同事
is one big "Fuck you" to the people
却在爆炸中不幸牺牲的人来说
Who would've been your coworkers,
就相当于一个巨大的"操"字
Except they perished in a blast right out there.
如果你一定要戴它  如果真的非戴不可
So if you need to wear it, if you really need to,
这是你的权利
Which is your right,
但你最好是我们所见过的最好的分析师
You better be the best analyst we've ever seen,
所以别跟我说什么没有异常
And that means don't tell me there's nothing.
给我个计划
Give me a plan.
要么给我个计划  要么就他妈闭嘴
Give me a goddamn plan or don't say anything.
清楚了吗
Is that clear?
现在你明白我们想做什么了吗
You understand the mission now, what we're trying to do here?
是
Yes.
很好
Good.
我
I...
又怎么了
What?
我有个计划
I have a plan.
你说
Well, tell it to me.
我们把这家银行的人带进来
We bring in people from this bank.
审问他们在中东的这三家银行支行的
Ask them about wire transfers from these three branches.
电汇情况
In the middle east.
而我们需要审问的银行工作人员
The bankers we want to talk to,
他们现在在纽约
They're in New York.
好  我会把他们带来
Okay, I'll get them down here.
明天我们就跟他们谈谈
We'll talk to them tomorrow.
我们俩一起
The two of us.
丹娜
Dana?
怎么了
What?
外头越来越冷了  你要加件毛衣吗
It's getting cold out. Do you want a sweater?
不用
I'm fine.
妈妈
Mom.
需要吃的吗
Something to eat?
-我说...  -妈  让她一个人呆会
- I said... - Mom, just leave her alone.
我只是问问她要不要吃的
I just asked if she wants some food.
别  你快把她逼疯了
Well, don't. You're driving her crazy.
一整天什么都没吃  肯定有事
When someone doesn't eat all day, it means something.
可能她只是不觉得饿
Maybe she's not hungry.
宝贝
Sweetie?
妈  真的  别
Mom, really, don't.
见鬼  卡莉
Shit, Carrie.
请坐
Have a seat.
我都不知道这事
I didn't know about this.
一听到消息我就赶过来了
I came as soon as I heard.
你是来把我弄出去的吗
Did you come to get me out?
我不能
I-I can't.
那滚吧
Just-just leave.
你不能到处泄露情报局的机密
You can't go around spilling agency secrets.
你知道的
You know that.
索尔都惊慌失措了
Saul's panicked.
因为我
About me.
因为不能确定中情局的将来
About the CIA, if it even has a future.
所以他把那场爆炸怪罪到我头上
So he blames the explosion on me.
这就是他拯救情报局的计划
That's his plan to save the agency.
-我知道这事很操蛋  -知道就好
- It's fucked up, I know. - Good.
-但这并不能让你离开这里  -不
-But it's not gonna get you out of here. - No.
不  明天我家人会出席听证会
No, my family will be at the hearing tomorrow,
-他们会把我弄出去的  -卡莉  你必须...
- And they will get me out. - Carrie, you have to...
必须什么  做该做的事吗
What? What do I have to do?
看看他们把我关在什么地方
Look where they put me.
没有什么是我必须做的
I don't have to do anything.
你要小心点
You have to be careful.
在爆炸前  在你甚至还没意识到的时候
There are things that happened before the explosions
发生了一些事
You're not even aware of.
他们针对...
People targeted...
我很担心你会受到伤害
I'm worried you're gonna get yourself hurt.
他派你来的  对吗
He sent you here, didn't he?
-谁  -索尔
- Who? - Saul.
他派你来恐吓我
He sent you to threaten me.
不  不是  他没派我来
No, no, he did not send me.
你走吧
Just leave.
你听我说好吗
Okay, would you just listen?
别管我
Leave me alone!
怎么了
What's going on?
没事吧
Are you okay?
什么事都没有
Everything is fine.
他马上就走了
He was just leaving.
丹娜
Dana?
丹娜  你在哪
Dana, where are you?
妈  怎么了
Mom, what happened?
你姐姐跑出去了
Your sister's gone.
从门那边走
Go through the door.
等等
Wait.
你还好吧
You okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
等等
Wait.
小心
Watch out.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我真的很需要见到你
I just really needed to see you.
麦琪
Maggie?
来了
Coming.
怎么了
What is it?
我需要找工资单
Pay stubs.
卡莉要在听证会上用到她的工资单
Carrie wants her paystubs for the hearing.
-为什么  -她说做证据用
- Why? - Well, she says it's evidence.
在那次该死的爆炸之后  她不止是复职
You know, they reinstated her after the damn explosion
还升官了
With a huge promotion.
如果这是她的错  你们真准备这么做吗
Is that what you do if it's her fault?
不过这又不是中情局受审判
It's not the CIA on trial though.
希望她能明白这点
Hope she gets that.
在这
Here.
真不敢相信你会来
I really can't believe you're here.
我能进去吗
Can I come in?
弗兰克  你好
Hello, Frank.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
对啊  你来干什么
Yeah, why are you here?
我...
Look, I, uh...
我知道你们现在很生气
I understand you're angry.
收起你的鳄鱼眼泪吧
Hey, skip the phony sympathy.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
我知道你们俩现在都很恨我
I know both of you hate me right now,
但是我是站在她这边的
But I'm on her side.
-扯淡  -我真的是
-Oh, bullshit. - I am.
但是这改变不了她现在正在走上歪路
Doesn't change the fact that the way she's carrying on,
她最大的敌人就是她自己
She's her own worst enemy.
你们得把她拉回来  她不能
You need to reign her in; she can't be running
一不高兴了就跑去找记者
To a reporter every time she gets upset.
她这么做了吗
Is that what she did?
她没跟你提过吗
What, she didn't even mention it to you?
-没有  -你想让她做什么
- No. - Well, what do you expect her to do?
打不还手吗
Not even fight back?
她不是在还击
She's not fighting back.
她是在让自己变成众矢之的
She's making herself a target.
中情局靠机密吃饭
Agency runs on secrecy.
有人希望她被刑事起诉
There are people who want her indicted on criminal charges.
你这是威胁我们吗
So you're threatening us?
我只是在告诉你们事实
I'm telling you the truth.
现在你们能为卡莉做的最有益的事
Best thing you can do for Carrie right now
是说服她待在里面
Is convince her to stay inside.
你是说那个精神病房吗
You mean the psych ward?
我是说一个无法监视的但能让她恢复的地方
I mean out of sight, someplace she can level out.
你知道她停药了  对吧
You know she's off her meds, right?
你不会也觉得那是个好办法吧
Unless you think that's a good idea,
你真的得帮帮我
You really have to help me.
真好
Good.
什么
What?
你在笑
You're smiling.
你也是
So are you.
我也奇怪为什么会笑出来
Wonder why that is.
他们很快就会发现
You know they're gonna find out soon
我不见了
That I'm missing.
还有你妈妈...
And your mother is just...
别说了
Don't.
求你了
Please.
我只想要这二人世界
Just want it to be us.
还有洗衣机
And appliances.
我只想要二人世界和这洗衣机
I just want it to be us and appliances.
因为我们没有毛病
'cause we're not defective.
知道吗
You know?
我们没有
We're not.
外面的一切才有毛病
It's everything out there.
那我宁愿在这里做个疯子
Then I'd rather stay here with all the other crazies.
你才不疯
You're not crazy.
如果我真是疯子呢
So what if I am?
你真的好帅
You're so beautiful.
他说如果你有需要
He says he's here
他可以来帮你做人品证人
as a character witness, if you need him.
我跟他说过不用了
I already told him I don't.
要是你吵吵闹闹把他折腾走了
If you make a fuss and have him removed,
恐怕法官那边不会有什么好印象
I don't think it'll help you with the magistrate.
多个帮自己的又没坏处
It's not bad to have someone else on your side.
那好吧  让他留下
Okay, fine. Just leave him then.
我机会有多少
So what are my chances?
我们会申请放你回家
We're asking that you be released to your family.
就我来看
So as far as I'm concerned,
机会很大
they're excellent.
感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
我只想赶紧了结
I just want this to be over.
他们可算来了
Oh, good, they're here.
麦琪  爸爸  嗨
Maggie, dad, hi.
这位是哈伦医生
This is Dr. Harlan.
嗨
Hey.
-都弄到了吧  -是的
- Did you find everything? - Yeah.
很好  我还在想你跑哪去了
Okay. I was wondering where you were.
这什么
What's this?
我们想谈谈你用药的事
We want to talk about your medication.
显然你们都商量好了
Obviously, you already have.
-卡莉  听我说  -不  几分钟后
- Carrie, listen... - No, I've got a hearing
我就有个听证会
in about three minutes.
关键就是我不想
The whole point being that I don't need
任人摆布
anyone telling me what to do.
你们还说要帮忙
You said you would help.
-我们是在帮你  -你们这叫帮倒忙
- We are helping.  -No, not when you pull this shit!
我们担心你啊
We're concerned, okay?
-怕你出问题  -省省吧
- About you getting yourself into trouble. - Don't be.
你那些话让人担心
I mean, from what you've been saying.
我什么都没说过
I've been saying nothing!
过去24小时
I've spent the last 24 hours
-我一直关在这里  -不  是之前
- checked in here. - No, before that.
你说记者那事啊
Oh, you mean the reporter.
对
Yes.
你又是怎么知道
You want to tell me
记者那事的
how you even know about that?
操  索尔那混蛋
God... fucking Saul.
他也是担心你
He's worried about you.
是吗
Really?
你那是泄露机密
You're divulging classified stuff.
他说句担心我
He told you that he was worried about me,
你们就真信了
and you believed it,
正是他把我弄进这里的
when he's the one who put me in here.
天呐  他这是要...
God, he's... he's try...
他这是要彻底整死我
he's trying to crush me when I am trying
而我还在苦苦
so hard to do what's...
找寻真相
what's right.
操
Fuck.
他简直人面兽心  根本不是朋友
No, he pretended to be my friend, and he's not.
说句难听的
You know what, really?
你们也一样
no different than you.
别这样
Hey...
大家起立
All rise.
巡回听证会第六场
The sixth circuit,
有请弗吉尼亚州
the Commonwealth of Virginia,
特别法官威廉・切斯尼
the honorable special justice William Chesney.
卡莉・麦吉森一案
Matter of Carrie Mathison.
是你吗
Is that you?
法官大人
Your honor...
对不起
I'm sorry.
闪开
Get off!
不
No!
这他妈是个骗局
This is a fucking sham!
快走
Come on.
恕我冒昧  长期以来
With all respect, you've had a long history
贵方与伊朗方面都有可疑交易
of questionable transactions with iran.
根据货币管理署出具的四号物证
Item four from the office of the controller of the currency,
三年前的十月间  他们曾下发一份
three years ago in October, they issued a cease and desist
要求你的当事人与德黑兰阿斯卡利银行
ordering your client to stop dealings
终止业务往来的禁止令
with the Al Askari Bank in Tehran.
我的当事人的确执行了禁令
My client complied with that order.
但你们仍旧与其贸易公司进行交易
You continued dealings with their trading company.
该禁令只限于银行业者
The order applied only to the bank.
是你们自己定义的吗
That's your position?
是禁令上的白纸黑字
That's the language in the paper.
于是在此期间  你们通过电子转账
So you proceeded to accept wire transfers
从某伊朗贸易公司
from an iranian trading company to the tune of $900 million
累计收款9亿美元
over that time period.
还有组织有计划
Systematically altered
篡改交易方抬头
the transaction headers
企图掩盖资金的真正来源
to conceal the true source of the funds.
我们并不知晓你们情报的来源
We're not sure where you're getting your information from.
我的当事人已尽了全力履行联邦法规
My client made every effort to comply with federal regulations.
我们有电邮显示结果迥然
We have an e-mail here saying the opposite.
有一条对哈兹拉文贸易公司的指令中写着
An instruction to Al Hazlawin Trading:
"删除所有伊朗方面客户的名称
"Delete all Iranian customer names to avoid any sign
以免为美方留下法律破绽"
of U.S. legal breach."
这些法律破绽
These legal breaches,
就是对你刚口口声声
those are violations of the laws
说你们在遵从的联邦律法的亵渎
you just told me you were complying with.
我不知您所指是什么
I wouldn't know what it refers to.
你怎么会不知道  邮件就是你发的
How can you not know? You sent the e-mail.
标题就是《勿提及伊朗》
Subject line is "Do not reference Iran."
我们掌握了虚假电子转账交易
We have the phony wire transfers--
成千上万笔
thousands of them.
我们想要真正交易者的名称
We want the real ones with the real names.
你们从哪儿搞来的
Where did you get this?
这就是你的问题吗
That's your question?
你的当事人在资助对本国的恐怖袭击
Your client is funding attacks by terrorists on this country,
而你却只想知道我们情报的来源
and all you want to know is how did we find out?
你刚才说的是谁来着
So who did you say this is again?
你们了解你们的银行吗
You know your bank?
它自鸦片战争起
It's been trafficking in human misery
便一直从事罪恶勾当
since the opium wars.
这不是过失
That's not an aberration.
也并非疏漏
It's not a mistake.
这就是你们的商业计划
That's your business plan.
你们为武器禁运国转移资金
You move money for embargoed governments
做虚假募捐
or phony charities.
至于资金用途  你们不闻不问
Where it goes, you don't want to know,
只要能赚到佣金就行了
as long as you get your fee.
但是这次我们要告诉你们钱去了哪里
But we're telling you where it went this time.
是用在了一辆载满C4炸药的汽车上
Into an suv full of c4 that blew up
就在三个月前  就在这幢楼的外面
right outside this building three months ago.
你们进来的时候还驶过了爆炸点
You passed the blast site on your way in.
我们知道资金经由你们的银行转移
We know the funds moved through your bank.
但我们还想知道资金的源头
We need to know where they originated.
是吗
You do?
是的
Yes.
抱歉  女士
All respect, ma'am...
在美国  这样可寻求不到帮助
in this country, that's not the way we ask for help.
你就完全没想过
Did you think for even a second
我有多担心吗
how worried I would be?
没必要担心
There was no need to worry.
怎么会没必要
How do you figure that?
他配不上你
He's not good for you.
凭什么这么说  你完全不了解他
And that is based on what, not knowing him at all?
显然他有问题
He's got problems, obviously.
不稳定
He's unstable.
这是你的专家诊断吗
Is that your professional diagnosis, mom?
他...丹娜  现在你需要的不是他
He's... Dana, he's not what you need right now.
也许我需要的正是他呢
Maybe he's exactly what I do need.
丹娜  康复中心每个医生  每册资料
Dana, every doctor at the center, every pamphlet,
还有我看过的每本书
every book that I've read on getting well,
都告诉我们相同的事
they all say the same thing:
就是现在最好先不要恋爱
you don't want to start a relationship.
什么  即便碰到真正懂你的人吗
What, with someone who actually understands you?
他们是这样说的吗
Is that what they say?
你知道这有多白痴吗
Do you realize how crazy that is?
你以为那帮人有什么真本事
You think they know something, the people in here.
其实屁也不是
Well, they don't.
就会神叨叨鬼话连篇
They just yack and yack and yack
直到埋单的人心里平衡些为止
until the people who are paying for it feel better.
好像真被他们治好了似的
Like everyone is getting well.
我真的无法理解
I really don't understand.
那就对了
Yeah, that's right.
你没事就好
Hey, glad you're all right.
哪里没事了
I'm not all right.
妈  没关系
Mom, it's okay.
是吗
Is it?
她跑到疯人院去还没关系
When someone runs away to the nuthouse?
她到底想让我怎么样
What does she want me to do?
你是想引起我注意吗
Do you want my attention?
是这样吗
Is that it?
我现在注意力都在你身上  真的
Because you got it, completely, believe me.
你想干嘛
What are you doing?
我不是想引起注意
I wasn't looking for attention.
丹娜  你想干嘛
Dana, what are you doing?
给你看些东西
Showing you something.
放开
No, no!
我并不想让你听到我哭喊呼救
It wasn't a cry for help what I did.
我并不想引起任何人注意
I didn't want anyone's attention.
我当时真的想自杀
I wanted to kill myself.
我想死了就一了百了
I wanted it all to be over, and I wanted to die
因为我已经受不了了
because I could not stand it anymore!
但我现在能承受了
But now I can.
我现在想活着
Now I want to be alive.
利奥就是原因
And the reason for that is Leo.
都不知道从什么时候起
I was happy last night for the first time
我很久没像昨晚那样开心过了
since I-I don't even know when.
我不想再这样下去
And I am not gonna do this anymore.
我不会再让别人对我指手画脚了
I am not gonna let everybody tell me what I should be fucking thinking
就好像我自己不能做决定一样
all the time, like I can't decide for myself,
好像我脑子真有毛病一样
like something is wrong with me.
利奥没疯
Because Leo is not crazy,
我也没疯
and I am not crazy.
你在怀疑自己疯了吗  你也没疯
And in case you're wondering, neither are you.
爸爸才疯了
Dad was crazy.
他有很多面
He was a lot of things.
他是个从一踏进家门起
He was a psycho who did nothing but lie
就满嘴谎言并破坏我们生活的
from the minute he set foot in this house,
不折不扣的疯子
and he ruined our lives.
这就是事实
It's the truth.
但我现在没事了
But I am okay now.
我真的好了  我敢这么说
I really am. I can... I can tell.
你知道为什么吗
Because you know what?
因为现在  此刻
Right now, at this moment,
我想活下去
I want to be alive.
银行那边有消息吗
Any word from the bankers?
没有
Nothing.
但我接到30个国会议员的电话
I did get calls from about 30 congressmen though.
让你停手
Telling you to back off.
提醒我该去抓恐怖分子
Remind me I'm supposed to be catching terrorists,
而不是搞垮国际银行系统
not bringing down the international banking system.
坐
Sit.
不用  我站着
No, I'll stand.
我今天去了卡莉的听证会
I went to Carrie's hearing today,
我看到她被拉下庭
and I saw her being hauled off,
乱踢乱叫
kicking and screaming.
我听说她失控了
I heard she lost it.
不是她失控了
She didn't lose it.
是我们让她失控了
We did that to her.
是我们
We did it.
我不会中途退出
I would never bail on you in the middle of something,
但我想让你知道  这里发生的事情
but I want you to know what's going on here
我无法接受
is not okay with me.
彼得
Peter...
这周确实难熬
It's been a rough week.
我懂
I'm aware.
但我们现在有了方向
But we're onto something.
如果跟我的预期一致
And if it leads to where I think,
这一切都值得
it will all have been worth it.
我不确定  索尔
I don't know, Saul.
有点信心吧
Just have a little faith.
问题就是
The thing is,
我没有
I don't.
这事一结束  我就走人
And when this is over, I'm out.
等事情结束再做决定吧
We'll see when we get there.
现在就说定了
I'm telling you now.
那是个意外  彼得
It was a mistake, Peter.
那孩子的死是个意外
What happened to that child.
没错  但那是我造成的
Yeah. It was my mistake.
我会处理
And I'll deal with it.
但我真不明白我们到底要干什么
But I don't know what the hell we're doing, I really don't.
我今天在中情局看到你了
I saw you at Langley today.
抱歉  我不认识你
Sorry, I don't remember.
可以理解
That's understandable.
你现在正忙着想方设法扯谎呢
You were pretty busy lying your ass off.
什么
What?
这周你失去了一个同事
You lost a colleague this week.
-没错  -他和他儿子都被枪杀了
- That's right. - He was gunned down, his son, too.
这是个可怕的意外
It was a horrible mistake.
希望不会重演
I hope it's not repeated.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
你是谁
Who are you?
别人不回答你的问题
It's aggravating, isn't it,
很让人恼火  是吧
when someone won't answer your questions?
-跟我律师谈  -我就跟你谈
- Talk to my lawyer... - I'm talking to you.
我还要告诉你  你现在还有得选
And I'm telling you, you have a choice.
你可以给我们需要的信息
You can give us the information we're asking for,
不然你就跟自己打哑谜吧
or you can keep up your stupid charade.
但如果你选择后者
But if you make the latter,
我会竭尽全力
I want you to know I try very hard
让你们这些贪官好看
to be patient with venal shitheads like you...
现在我只能做这么多了
But I can only do it so long.
祝你平安飞到家
You have a good flight home.
都在这了吗
They're all here?
-银行记录  -应该都在
- The records? - Seem to be.
能从中找到什么线索
So what'd they give us?
所有线索
Everything.
银行基本都不管禁止令
HLBC basically ignored the cease and desist order,
和我们讨论的一样
just like we said.
他们虽然停止与阿斯卡里银行[巴基斯坦]合作
They stopped dealing with al-Askari bank,
但仍在与贸易公司合作
but they continued with the trading company.
实际上  交易额反而增加了
In fact, the number of transactions increased,
尤其是接近爆炸的日子
especially toward the date of the explosion.
查到涉及此事的所有人了吗
Know who all was involved?
还在查
We're getting there.
我们通过最终收款人已经确定了
On the receiving end, we've already identified
大约一半与阿布・纳齐尔有联系的人
half a dozen known associates of Abu Nazir.
资金来源呢
What about the source?
我们把名字输入交易记录中
We're still putting names to the transactions,
全部指向伊朗
but it's all pointing to Iran.
不仅仅是这个国家
Not just the country.
而是直接指向政府内部
Inside the government.
他们为什么会突然决定合作了
So why did they suddenly decide to cooperate?
不确定  我们该查清楚
I'm not sure. We want to know.
这是什么
What is this?
我横向比较各个账户时发现的
Something I noticed when I was reconciling the accounts horizontally.
所有来自伊朗的资金有20%流向了银行
All the Iranian funds had 20% stripped off by our banker friends--
这是处理违法交易的标准收费
a standard fee for prohibited transactions.
但  其中四分之一不见了
But... a quarter of that disappeared.
去哪儿了
To where?
还不清楚
I don't know yet.
就凭空消失了
Just seems to have vanished.
反正银行没有吞这笔钱
All I know is it was not retained by their bank.
查清楚
Find it.
-查清楚这钱到哪儿去了  -我尽力
- Find out where it went. - I'm trying.
这是你的首要任务
Make it your number one priority.
这些钱就是关键
That right there, that's the key.
近四千五百万美元
Almost $45 million.
法拉
Fara...
是  长官
Yes, sir?
这事先暂时保密
Keep it between us, for the time being.
我不知道你想证明什么
I don't know what you think you're proving.
但大家只是想让你服药
All anyone's asking is that you take your meds.
这是你逼我们的
I mean, you're not leaving us any choice.
这就是你想要的吗
Is that what you want?
她在那边
Right over there.
卡莉
Carrie.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
操...
Fuck...
你妈  索尔
You, Saul.